Ronald G. Becker Collection of Charles Eisenmann Photographs
Ronald G. Becker collection of Charles Eisenmann photographs
- Ronald G. Becker collection of sideshow memorabilia (Box 12)
  - 1123-159 - Serpentine born with no bones except skull (Box 15)
  - 1123-160 - Dolores Connatto fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-161 - Pony Boy walks on all fours very skinny legs (Box 15)
  - 1123-162 - Klikko African bushman with Ringling Bros. (Box 15)
  - 1123-163 - Thelma Ward Pony girl large spots from which coarse hair grew (Box 15)
  - 1123-164 - Fanny Miles enormous feet, 1880 (Box 15)
  - 1123-165 - Unidentified picture of side show attractions (Box 15)
  - 1123-166 - Mina and Minnie Finley Siamese twins joined at the bottom (Box 15)
  - 1123-167 - Lod Skeleton midget with deformed arms and legs (Box 15)
  - 1123-168 - Bonita midget fat girl with Dreamland Circus, 1913 (Box 15)
  - 1123-169 - Unidentified fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-170 - Elora May King colored fat lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-171 - Japanese tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-172 - Unidentified tattooed man (Box 15)
  - 1123-173 - Unidentified tattooed woman (Box 15)
  - 1123-174 - Hazel Mackly tattooed lady, 1933 (Box 15)
  - 1123-175 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-176 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-177 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-178 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-179 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-180 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-181 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-182 - Unidentified tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-183 - Unidentified tattooed person (Box 15)
  - 1123-184 - Unidentified tattooed man (Box 15)
  - 1123-185 - Unidentified man with elephant (Houdini?) (Box 15)
  - 1123-186 - Robert Earl Hughes fat man, 1957 (Box 15)
  - 1123-187 - Jean Carson tattooed lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-188 - Eleven year old Boston girl contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-189 - Eleven year old Boston girl contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-190 - William "Twisto" D'Andrea contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-191 - Hal Plummer, Jr. contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-192 - Eleven year old Boston girl contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-193 - Mary Jacquelyn Terry contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-194 - Eagan Twist contortionist shown with wife and sister (Box 15)
  - 1123-195 - Jean Libberro parasitic Siamese twin (Box 15)
  - 1123-196 - F.C. Roland India rubber man contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-197 - Capt. M.V. Bates giant, with normal man and short man F. Bowman (Box 15)
  - 1123-198 - Unize albino bushy hair and Mlle. Zenobia bushy haired lady (Box 15)
  - 1123-199 - Siamese calves (Box 15)
  - 1123-200 - Dolly living two headed cow, 1951 (Box 15)
  - 1123-201 - Siamese calves (Box 15)
  - 1123-202 - A hen with no bill (Box 15)
  - 1123-203 - Siamese calves (Box 15)
  - 1123-204 - Two legged calf (Box 15)
  - 1123-205 - Mary Jacquelyn Terry contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1123-206 - Patty Kriel contortionist (Box 15)
  - 1124-1 - Unidentified circus wagons and elephants (Box 15)
  - 1124-2 - Seil's Sterling Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-3 - Seil's Sterling Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-4 - Seil's Sterling Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-5 - Al G. Barnes Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-6 - Barnum and Bailey Circus - sketch, 1883 (Box 15)
  - 1124-7 - Jumbo of Barnum and Bailey sketch, 1882 (Box 15)
  - 1124-8 - John and Carrie Rooney of Barnum and Bailey, 1906 (Box 15)
  - 1124-9 - Barnum's Orchestmelchor, 1873 (Box 15)
  - 1124-10 - Lena of Power's Elephants, 1905 (Box 15)
  - 1124-11 - Downie Bros. Circus, 1932 (Box 15)
  - 1124-12 - Downie Bros. Circus, 1932 (Box 15)
  - 1124-13 - Downie Bros. Circus, 1932 (Box 15)
  - 1124-14 - Downie Bros. Circus, 1932 (Box 15)
  - 1124-15 - Adam Forpaugh shows (Box 15)
  - 1124-16 - Adam H. Paw shows (Box 15)
  - 1124-17 - Haag Bros. Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-18 - Haag Bros. Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-19 - Hagenbeck Wallace Circus, 1920 (Box 15)
  - 1124-20 - Hagenbeck Wallace Circus, 1934 (Box 15)
  - 1124-21 - Hagenbeck Wallace Circus, 1934 (Box 15)
  - 1124-22 - Hagenbeck Wallace Circus, 1934 (Box 15)
  - 1124-23 - Hagenbeck Wallace Circus, 1934 (Box 15)
  - 1124-24 - Jones' Bros. World Toured Shows, 1915 (Box 15)
  - 1124-25 - James M. June and Co.'s Circus advertisement, 1850 (Box 15)
  - 1124-26 - The Great London Circus advertisement (Box 15)
  - 1124-27 - Fred Aymar portrait Equestrian Dir. of Walter L. Main Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-28 - Archie Royes Portrait Clown for Walter L. Main Circus, 1893 (Box 15)
  - 1124-29 - Tom Mix Circus, 1936 (Box 15)
  - 1124-30 - Newton Bros. Circus and Indian Shows Winter Barn, 1872 (Box 15)
  - 1124-31 - Dan Rice's Trick Horse, Exelsior (Box 15)
  - 1124-32 - Dan Rice Home (Box 15)
  - 1124-33 - Dan Rice Circus shown in picture of Jamestown, NY, 1864 (Box 15)
  - 1124-34 - Ringling Bros. Mounted Band, 1897 (Box 15)
  - 1124-35 - Ringling Bros. 8 Horse Team Band Wagon (Box 15)
  - 1124-36 - Fred Buchanan's Yankee Robinson Circus, 1908 (Box 15)
  - 1124-37 - John Wilson Portrait Horse Director of Robinson Show (Box 15)
  - 1124-38 - John Robinson's Circus (Box 15)
  - 1124-39 - John Robinson's Circus, 1900 (Box 15)
  - 1124-40 - Sells Floto Circus, 1929 (Box 15)
  - 1124-41 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-42 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931; duplicate of #1124-41 (Box 15)
  - 1124-43 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1921 (Box 15)
  - 1124-44 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-45 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-46 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-47 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-48 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-49 - Spark's R.R. Circus, 1931 (Box 15)
  - 1124-50 - The Great Wallace Circus, 1904 (Box 15)
  - 1124-51 - Unidentified Circus: dog and horse act (Box 15)
  - 1124-52 - Unidentified circus dog act (Box 15)
  - 1124-53 - Unidentified circus dog act (Box 15)
  - 1124-54 - Unidentified circus dog act (Box 15)
  - 1124-55 - Four picture set of unidentified circus parade wagons (Box 15)
  - 1124-56 - George H. Adams portrait clown (Box 15)
  - 1124-57 - Zazel the Human Cannonball, 1878 (Box 15)
  - 1124-58 - Educated horse and trainer (Box 15)
  - 1124-59 - McIntire and Heath, 1879 (Box 15)
  - 1124-60 - Ad for the benefit for Laura Keene on the day of Lincoln's assassination - 4/14/1865 (Box 15)
  - 1124-61 - Headquarters of General William Tecumseh Sherman, 1864 (Box 15)
  - 1125 - Comm. Nutt, 1870 (Box 17)
  - 1126 - Sideshow troupe, 1930 (Box 17)
  - 1127 - Sideshow troupe, 1930; duplicate of #1126 (Box 17)
  - 1128 - Sideshow troupe, 1890 (Box 17)
  - 1129 - Sideshow troupe, 1890; close-up of #1128 (Box 17)
  - 1130 - Ubangi savages, 1930 (Box 17)
  - 1131 - Outdoor sideshow scene, 1923 (Box 17)
  - 1132 - The Gaiety Museum 138 Bowery (Box 17)
  - 1133 - Performers in front of a Dime Museum, 1920 (Box 17)
  - 1134 - Outdoor view of a dime museum, 1920 (Box 17)
  - 1135 - Gleason's Pictorial Magazine view of Barnum's American Museum, 1853 (Box 19)
  - 1136 - Gleason's Pictorial Magazine view of Barnum's American Museum, 1853 (Box 19)
  - 1137 - Gleason's Pictorial Magazine The Bearded Lady of Geneva, 1853 (Box 19)
  - 1138 - Gleason's Pictorial Magazine Chang & Eng and Wives and Children, 1853 (Box 19)
  - 1139 - Charles Edwards, tattooed man and sword walker, 1905 (Box 19)
  - 1140 - Madam Clofullia the Swiss bearded lady, 1865 (Box 19)
  - 1141 - P.T. Barnum's Illustrated Newspaper, 1878 (Box 19)
  - 1142 - P.T. Barnum's Greatest Show on Earth Newspaper, 1881 (Box 19)
  - 1143 - Singer's Midgets, 1930 (Box 19)
  - 1144 - Singer's Midgets, 1930 (Box 19)
  - 1145 - Singer's Midgets, 1930 (Box 19)
  - 1146 - One of Singer's Midgets, 1930 (Box 19)
  - 1147 - Strong man, 1930 (Box 19)
  - 1148 - High caste Hindoo's Eisenmann (Box 13)
  - 1149 - Zulu Warriors, princess and child Eisenmann (Box 13)
  - 1150 - Lionel lion-faced boy (Box 13)
  - 1151 - John Robinson Circus (Box 13)
  - 1152 - Unidentified fat man (Box 13)
  - 1153 - Burmese hairy family (Box 13)
  - 1154 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1155 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1156 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1157 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1158 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1159 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1160 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1161 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1162 - Blanch Gray (Box 13)
  - 1163 - Boy with breasts (Box 13)
  - 1164 - Unidentified fat boy in sailor suit (Box 13)
  - 1165 - Unidentified fat boy in sailor suit, close up of #1164 (Box 13)
  - 1166 - Unidentified fat man in military uniform (Box 13)
  - 1167 - Unidentified fat man in military uniform (Box 13)
  - 1168 - Unidentified fat man in military uniform (Box 13)
  - 1169 - Unidentified fat man in military uniform (Box 13)
  - 1170 - Woman holding deformed infant (Box 13)
  - 1171 - Mrs. Williams (Box 13)
  - 1172 - Portrait of fat woman with pearl necklace (Box 13)
  - 1173 - The Spaulding family, 1880 (Box 19)
  - 1174 - Barnum and Bailey Greatest Show on Earth, 1960; duplicate of #1175 (Box 19)
  - 1175 - Barnum and Bailey Greatest Show on Earth, duplicate of #1174 (Box 19)
  - 1176 - Freaks poster (Map-case 1, Drawer 1)
  - 1177 - Tickets to circus shows, 7 items (Box 17)
  - 1178 - Official route of Walter L. Main Circus 1923 season (Box 17)
  - 1179 - Hagenbeck's Arena and World's Museum program (Box 17)
  - 1180 - Sketch of the life of Charles S. Stratton, 1847 (Box 17)
  - 1181 - The Arenic World magazine (Box 19)
  - 1182 - A Case of Acromegaly booklet, 1910 (Box 17)
  - 1183 - Cure of a case of acute ulceratine endocarditis booklet, 1940 (Box 17)
  - 1184 - Osteopetrosis booklet, 1941 (Box 17)
  - 1185 - Chronic adrenal insufficiency booklet, 1933 (Box 17)
  - 1186 - Newer treatment of Parkinson's Syndrome booklet, 1940 (Box 17)
  - 1187 - General Tom Thumb (Box 18)
  - 1188 - Newspaper clippings about a variety of abnormal medical phenomena (Box 17)
  - 1189 - Negatives for book (Box 17)
  - 1190 - Research for a book (Box 17)
  - 1191 - Miss Bertha Curtis 540 lbs., oversize poster (Map-case 1, Drawer 1)
  - 1192 - Nora Hildebrandt, Tattooed Woman (Box 13)
  - 1193 - Nora Hildebrandt, Tattooed Woman (Box 13)
  - 1194 - Unidentified Tattooed Woman (Box 13)
  - 1195 - Unidentified Tattooed Woman (Box 13)
  - 1196 - Unidentified Tattooed Woman (Box 13)
  - 1197 - Irene, Tattooed Woman (Box 13)
  - 1198 - Lavinia Warren, Midget (Box 13)
  - 1199 - Gen. Tom Thumb and Wife, Commodore Nutt and Miss Minnie Warren, midgets (Box 13)
  - 1200 - Goats pulling carriage (Box 13)
  - 1201 - Unidentified midget man and woman (Box 13)
  - 1202 - Master John H. Powers, Fat Boy (Box 13)
  - 1203 - Mary J. Powers (Box 13)
  - 1204 - Unidentified Man (Box 13)
  - 1205 - Midgets in formal dress (Box 13)
  - 1206 - Unidentified midget woman (Box 13)
  - 1207 - Mr. and Mrs. General Tom Thumb (Box 13)